McKersie, Robert PIE Trucking Company Files 6325
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert McKersie PIE Trucking Company Files
1985-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McKersie, Robert
PIE Nationwide Trucking
6325
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records.
7506523
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 18, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
McKersie, Robert B.; Ryder/P. I. E. Nationwide Trucking Company
7506523
- Board of Directors' Meeting minutes (Box 1)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    November 21, 1985 - September 25, 1986
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    October 30, 1986 - August 7, 1987
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    August 25, 1987 - December 14, 1988
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    March 16, 1989 - January 23, 1990
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    February 13-14, 1990 - April 22, 1990
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    May 3, 1990 - December 15, 1990
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PIE Current [Folder 1 of 3], 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - PIE Current [Folder 2 of 3], 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - PIE Current [Folder 3 of 3], 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Presentation (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Director G. William BAAB, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Directors Contact Information and Notes (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bankruptcy, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Michael R. Lewis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Michael R. Lewis, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - McKersie Court Case Against Sale of PIE [Folder 1 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - McKersie Court Case Against Sale of PIE [Folder 2 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Pugh Depostion transcript and exhibits (Box 2)
  - Pugh Deposition Transcript pp.5-206 (with Index) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Pugh Deposition Transcript pp.207-385 (with Index) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Pugh Deposition Transcript pp.386-522 (with Index) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pugh Deposition Exhibits Plaintiff's No.1-14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pugh Deposition Exhibits Plaintiff's No.15-31 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pugh Deposition Exhibits Plaintiff's No.32-43 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pugh Deposition Exhibits Plaintiff's No.44-65 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pugh Deposition Exhibits Plaintiff's No.66-82 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pugh Deposition Exhibits Plaintiff's No.84-87 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Court Transcripts Case 92-14636-CA (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Court Transcripts Case 92-14638-CA (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Court Transcripts Case 92-14642-CA (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - MX14 0338-0482 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - MX14 0483-0611 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - MX14 0612-0739 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - IU International Corporation (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Notes from Meetings (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Reports, Court transcripts, Board of Directors' meeting minutes (Box 3)
  - Defendant's Exhibit 27 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Defendant's Exhibit 28 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Case No. 92-14642-CA (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Deposition Roger V. Pugh, Jr. Volume I, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    March 23-25, 1995
  - Transcript Case No. 92-14642-CA (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Plaintiff's Exhibit 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits to Keyko Opinion Volume I (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits to Keyko Opinion Volume II (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Deposition Roger V. Pugh, Jr. Volume II, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)